Guide to the Cedric N. Chatterley Photographs, 1983-2013 and undated RL.00219
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Holy Land USA Series, 1985-1986 and undated, 3 boxes; 50 prints and 1 item
  - Weathered display near chapel (printed 2001). Holy Land, USA, Waterbury, CT, 1986 (Box 6)
  - Wall near chapel (printed 2001). Holy Land, USA, Waterbury, CT, 1986 (Box 6)
  - Top of the hill, overlooking Waterbury (printed 2001). Holy Land, USA, Waterbury, CT, 1986 (Box 6)
  - Glass display case (printed 2001). Holy Land, USA, Waterbury, CT, 1986 (Box 6)
  - Display on hillside (printed 2001). Holy Land, USA, Waterbury, CT, 1986 (Box 6)
  - Display near Catacombs (printed 2001). Holy Land, USA, Waterbury, CT, 1986 (Box 6)
  - Inside the Catacombs (printed 2001). Holy Land, USA, Waterbury, CT, 1986 (Box 6)
  - Display inside the Catacombs (printed 2001). Holy Land, USA, Waterbury, CT, 1986 (Box 6)
  - Display inside Catacombs (printed 2001). Holy Land, USA, Waterbury, CT, 1986 (Box 6)
  - Holy Land, USA, Waterbury, CT. Photographed 1986, printed 2001. Archivally processed. Original Oriental Seagull paper. (Box 6)
  - Holy Land Replica. Waterbury, Conn. - 11.25x17.5 inch color placemat (Box 14)
- MFA Thesis Series, 1987, 2 boxes; 43 prints
  Consists of three 11x14 inch and 40 18x24 inch gelatin silver prints for Chatterley's Master of Fine Arts thesis at Southern Illinois University at Carbondale, entitled Ambivalent Ecstasies/Converging Energies. This body of work explores religious ecstatic experience. The three 11x14 prints offer a panoramic shot of the thesis exhibit, while the forty 18x24 prints form the body of work for the thesis project. The prints have no captions but are numbered sequentially, with information included that indicates their positions in the exhibit, and the date of the exhibit, May 6, 1987.
  - 11x14 Prints
    - 11x14 print titled MFA thesis exhibit, Southern Illinois University, Carbondale, IL, 1987 May 6 (Box 7)
    - MFA thesis exhibit, Southern Illinois University, Carbondale, IL (Box 7)
    - MFA thesis exhibit (self-portrait), Southern Illinois University, Carbondale, IL (Box 7)
  - 18x24 Prints
    - MFA thesis #1 (Box 7)
    - MFA thesis #2 (Box 7)
    - MFA thesis #3 (small cross dangling from hand-held Bible) (Box 7)
    - MFA thesis #4 top (above #5) (Box 7)
    - MFA thesis #5 bottom (below #4) (Box 7)
    - MFA thesis #6 top (above #7) (Box 7)
    - MFA thesis #7 bottom (below #6) (Box 7)
    - MFA thesis #8 top (above #9) (Box 7)
    - MFA thesis #9 bottom (below #8) (Box 7)
    - MFA thesis #10 top (above #11) (Box 7)
    - MFA thesis #11 bottom (below #10) (Box 7)
    - MFA thesis #12 top (above #13) (Box 7)
    - MFA thesis #13 bottom (below #12) (Box 7)
    - MFA thesis #14 top (above #15) (Box 7)
    - MFA thesis #15 bottom (below #14) (Box 7)
    - MFA thesis #16 top (above #17) (Box 7)
    - MFA thesis #17 bottom (below #16) (Box 7)
    - MFA thesis #18 top (above #19), with open Bible (Box 7)
    - MFA thesis #19 bottom (below #18) (Box 7)
    - MFA thesis #20 top (above #21), Bible/pulpit (Box 8)
    - MFA thesis #21 bottom (below #20) (Box 8)
    - MFA thesis #22 top (above #23) (Box 8)
    - MFA thesis #23 bottom (below #22) (Box 8)
    - MFA thesis #24 top (above #25) (Box 8)
    - MFA thesis #25 bottom (below #24) (Box 8)
    - MFA thesis #26 top (above #27) (Box 8)
    - MFA thesis #27 bottom (below #26) (Box 8)
    - MFA thesis #28 top (above #29) (Box 8)
    - MFA thesis #29 bottom (below #28) (Box 8)
    - MFA thesis #30 top (above #31) (Box 8)
    - MFA thesis #31 bottom (below #30, top) (Box 8)
    - MFA thesis #32 top (above #33) (Box 8)
    - MFA thesis #33 bottom (below #32) (Box 8)
    - MFA thesis #34 top (above #35) (Box 8)
    - MFA thesis #35 bottom (below #34) (Box 8)
    - MFA thesis #36 top (above #37) (Box 8)
    - MFA thesis #37 bottom (below #36) (Box 8)
    - MFA thesis #38 (Box 8)
    - MFA thesis #39 (Box 8)
    - MFA thesis #40 (Box 8)
- Penobscot Poultry Series, 1988-1994, 6 boxes; 101 prints
  Consists of 91 11x14 inch and 10 16x20 inch gelatin silver prints. On February 24, 1988, Penobscot Poultry in Belfast, Maine closed down. Chatterley documented the final days of the last chicken processing plant in the state and followed former employee Linda Lord as she sought new employment afterwards. The plant became the subject of the book, I Was Content and Not Content: The Story of Linda Lord and the Closing of Penobscot Poultry by Alicia J. Rouverol and Stephen A. Cole, with Chatterley contributing the photographs. Original captions, with Chatterley's contextual side comments, were taken from back of prints. Arranged chronologically.
  - Linda Lord at work in the "blood tunnel" (I did not know she was there when I made this photograph during the first tour in mid-February, 1988). Penobscot Poultry, Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb. (Box 9)
  - Workers taking a break inside Penobscot Poultry, Belfast, Maine, (final day) 1988 Feb. 24 (Box 9)
  - Two workers in the break room not far from the "blood tunnel" on Penobscot Poultry's final day, 1988 Feb. 24. Belfast, Maine. (Box 9)
  - Linda Lord and co-workers in the break room nearest the "blood tunnel" on Penobscot Poultry's closing day, Feb. 24, 1988. Belfast, Maine. (This was before I saw Linda at work inside the blood tunnel. I had not spoken to her yet or introduced myself.) (Box 9)
  - Workers turning in their smocks on the final day of Penobscot Poultry, Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb. 24 (Box 9)
  - Line worker and foreman embrace on the final day of Penobscot Poultry, Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb. 24 (Box 9)
  - Poultry barn near Brooks, Maine, 1988 Feb. (Box 9)
  - Poultry barn near Brooks, Maine, 1988 Feb. (Box 9)
  - Hatchery in Waldo County, Maine, 1988 Feb. (Box 9)
  - Worker at Bayside Industries Hatchery, Unity, Maine, 1988 Feb. (Box 9)
  - Husband and wife team "sexing" young chicks at Bayside Industries Hatchery near Unity, Maine, 1988 Feb. (Box 9)
  - Clean-up time, first visit to Penobscot Poultry, Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb. (Box 9)
  - Trucks with live chickens entering Penobscot Poultry, Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb. (Box 9)
  - Trucks with empty crates exiting Penobscot Poultry's loading dock-from the second story window. Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb. (Box 9)
  - Workers ("hangers") outside on the loading dock at Penobscot Poultry, Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb. (Box 9)
  - Workers ("hangers") outside on the loading dock at Penobscot Poultry, Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb. (Box 10)
  - Workers ("hangers") outside on the loading dock at Penobscot Poultry, Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb. (Box 10)
  - Dead chickens, expired before exiting their crates, loading dock at Penobscot Poultry, Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb. (Box 10)
  - Workers, boxes, ice, scale, roller conveyor inside Penobscot Poultry, Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb. (Box 10)
  - Poultry, after being hung, move toward Penobscot Poultry's interior. Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb. (Box 10)
  - Workers transferring poultry from conveyor to another. Penobscot Poultry, Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb. (Box 10)
  - Poultry after being run through the scalder and about to go into the de-feathering machine in Penobscot Poultry, Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb. (Box 10)
  - Poultry exiting the de-feathering machine in Penobscot Poultry, Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb. (Box 10)
  - Poultry coming out of the de-feathering machine. Penobscot Poultry, Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb. (Box 10)
  - Coming and going from the de-feathering machine. Penobscot Poultry, Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb. (Box 10)
  - One of several open flames to singe pinfeathers/hair. Penobscot Poultry, Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb. (Box 10)
  - Poultry shackled on a moving conveyor, passing a gas flame to remove hair, pinfeathers. Penobscot Poultry, Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb. (Box 10)
  - Poultry passing over gas-lit flame to remove pin-hairs/feathers. Inspector stands and inspects. Penobscot Poultry, Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb. (Box 10)
  - Inspector cutting away bruised parts. Penobscot Poultry, Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb. (Box 10)
  - Inspector cutting away bruised parts. Penobscot Poultry, Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb. (Box 10)
  - Inspectors at a conveyor belt inside Penobscot Poultry, Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb. (Box 10)
  - Inspector standing near window inside Penobscot Poultry-overlooking Penobscot Bay. Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb. (Box 11)
  - Workers on "Line One" inside Penobscot Poultry, Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb. (Box 11)
  - The "neck puller." Penobscot Poultry, Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb. (Box 11)
  - Necks in a holding tank. Penobscot Poultry, Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb. (Box 11)
  - The eviscerating line. Penobscot Poultry, Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb. (Box 11)
  - The eviscerating line. Penobscot Poultry, Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb. (Box 11)
  - Worker reaching in to pull intestines on the eviscerating line inside Penobscot Poultry, Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb. (Box 11)
  - Workers on the "cut up line" inside Penobscot Poultry, Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb. (Box 11)
  - Upstairs in "Further processing" inside Penobscot Poultry, Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb. (Box 11)
  - Upstairs in "Further processing" inside Penobscot Poultry, Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb. (Box 11)
  - Workers upstairs in "Further processing." Penobscot Poultry, Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb. (Box 11)
  - Workers upstairs in "Further processing." Penobscot Poultry, Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb. (Box 11)
  - Worker at machine that manages chicken hearts (and possibly gizzards) inside Penobscot Poultry, Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb. (Box 11)
  - Rendering room, Penobscot Poultry, Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb. (Box 11)
  - Penobscot Poultry, Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb. (Box 11)
  - Penobscot Poultry, Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb. (Box 11)
  - Penobscot Poultry, Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb. (Box 11)
  - Stacking ready to ship packages of chicken to be shipped. Penobscot Poultry, Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb. (Box 11)
  - Automatic neck-cutting device in the "blood tunnel" inside Penobscot Poultry, Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb. (Box 11)
  - Penobscot Poultry, Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb. (Box 11)
  - Penobscot Poultry, Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb. (Box 12)
  - Workers at the Cry-o-vac (bagging) machine. Penobscot Poultry, Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb. (Box 12)
  - Man with bagged sandwich watches a friend at the box machine. Penobscot Poultry, Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb. (Box 12)
  - Freezer lockers, Penobscot Poultry, Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb. (Box 12)
  - Break area, Penobscot Poultry, Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb. (Box 12)
  - Workers taking a break. Penobscot Poultry, Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb. (Box 12)
  - Worker looking for pocket change to put in the vending machine at Penobscot Poultry, Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb. (Box 12)
  - Hallway near lunchroom. Penobscot Poultry, Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb. (Box 12)
  - Announcement board inside Penobscot Poultry, Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb. (Box 12)
  - Hosing down - clean up time at Penobscot Poultry, Belfast, Maine, 1988 Feb. (Box 12)
  - Penobscot Poultry, center of image. Belfast, Maine, 1988 Mar. (Box 12)
  - Penobscot Poultry a few weeks after it closed. Belfast, Maine, 1988 Mar. (Box 12)
  - Linda Lord hanging clothes on her front porch. There is a plastic barrier to keep out winter winds. 1988, Mar. (Box 12)
  - Linda Lord helping her friend, Roxie, catch and slaughter a half-dozen chickens. Near Brooks, Maine, 1988 Mar. (Box 12)
  - Linda Lord in Roxie's yard-catching and slaughtering chickens. Near Brooks, Maine, 1988 Mar. (Box 12)
  - Linda Lord and her friend, Roxie, cutting up chickens. Near Brooks, Maine, 1988 Mar. (Box 12)
  - Linda Lord backing a truck into the Brooks Volunteer Fire Dept. building. Brooks, Maine, 1988 Mar. (Box 12)
  - Linda Lord backing a truck into the Brooks Volunteer Fire Dept. garage. Brooks, Maine, 1988 Mar. (Box 12)
  - Linda Lord (on top of truck) during routine fire drill. Brooks City Park, Brooks, Maine, 1988 Mar. (Box 12)
  - Linda Lord at a resume writing workshop inside the Belfast Curling Club, Belfast, Maine, 1988 Mar. (Box 12)
  - Two photographs of Linda Lord. On the back of one, her father, Philip, wrote: My sleepy time girl and her first deer. (The photographs are on Linda's kitchen table.) Brooks, Maine, 1988 Apr. (Box 13)
  - Linda Lord and others taking a test for Champion Paper Co. at the Coastal Economic Development Office. Belfast, Maine, 1988 Apr. (Box 13)
  - Linda Lord serving food at the Brooks Volunteer Fire Dept. Benefit Supper. Brooks, Maine, 1988 Apr. (Box 13)
  - Linda Lord at the Brooks Volunteer Fire Department Supper. Brooks, Maine, 1988 Apr. (Box 13)
  - Entering Brooks, Maine (from the south) on Rt. 7. 1988 Apr. (Box 13)
  - Chickens entering Penobscot Poultry, Belfast, Maine, 1988 June (Box 13)
  - Linda Lord crossing her front yard. (The house once belonged to her grandmother). Brooks, Maine, 1988 June (Box 13)
  - Linda Lord learning computer skills at the Coastal Economic Development Office. Belfast, Maine, 1988 June (Box 13)
  - Linda Lord checking the job announcement board at the Coastal Economic Development Office. Belfast, Maine, 1988 June (Box 13)
  - Linda Lord playing drums with the Golden Nuggets at a campground in Dixmont, Maine, 1988 June (Box 13)
  - Linda Lord playing drums with the Golden Nuggets at a campground in Dixmont, Maine, 1988 June (Box 13)
  - Linda Lord in the Brooks Volunteer Fire Dept. truck on her way to participate in a 4th of July parade in Unity, Maine, 1988. (Box 13)
  - Untitled print depicting Linda Lord affixing American flags to the Brooks Volunteer Fire Dept. truck on the July 4, 1988. (Box 13)
  - Belfast, Maine from Rt. 1. 1988 Summer. (Box 13)
  - Linda Lord looking into a rope-making machine inside Belfast Rope. Belfast, Maine, 1988 Sept. (Box 13)
  - Linda Lord untangling small material inside Belfast Rope during her first week. Belfast, Maine, 1988 Sept. (Box 13)
  - Phillip Lord (Linda's father), Linda, and Bandit in the garden behind their house in Brooks, Maine, 1992 Summer (Box 13)
  - Bandit giving Linda Lord a kiss in front of her home (where she was born) in Brooks, Maine, 1994 Summer (Box 13)
  - Linda Lord on her three-wheeled motorcycle in downtown Brooks, Maine, 1994 Summer (Box 13)
  - Downtown Belfast, Maine, 1994 Summer (Box 13)
  - 16x20 print of Linda Lord at work in the "blood tunnel" on Penobscot Poultry's final day of production, February 24, 1988. (Box 14)
  - 16x20 print of Linda Lord at work in the "blood tunnel" inside Penobscot Poultry on its final day of production, February 24, 1988. Belfast, Maine. (Box 14)
  - 16x20 print of Linda Lord at work in the "blood tunnel" inside Penobscot Poultry on its final day of production, February 24, 1988. Belfast, Maine. (Box 14)
  - 16x20 print of Linda Lord at work in the "blood tunnel" inside Penobscot Poultry on its last day of production, February 24, 1988. Belfast, Maine. (Box 14)
  - 16x20 print of Linda Lord at work in the "blood tunnel" inside Penobscot Poultry on its final day of production, February 24, 1988. Belfast, Maine. (Box 14)
  - 16x20 print of Linda Lord applying for unemployment benefits for the first time in her life. The American Legion Hall, Post 43, Belfast, Maine. 1988 Mar. 1 (Box 14)
  - 16x20 print of Linda Lord showing her high school senior portrait. Rollie's Cafe, Belfast, Maine, 1988 Mar. 15 (Box 14)
  - 16x20 print of Linda Lord at work in Belfast Rope. 1988 Sept. 12 (Box 14)
  - 16x20 print of Linda Lord at work. Belfast Rope, 1988 Sept. (Box 14)
  - 16x20 print of Linda Lord at work inside Belfast Rope. Belfast, Maine, 1988 Sept. (Box 14)
- David "Honeyboy" Edwards Series, 1990-1996 and undated, 4 boxes; 119 prints
  Consists of 119 11x14 selenium-toned gelatin silver prints and contact prints documenting Mississippi Delta blues guitarist David "Honeyboy" Edwards. Images were taken between 1990 and 1996. They feature Edwards and the places he visited while touring the southern and midwestern United States, including Arkansas, Chicago, and Louisiana, and images of Honeyboy visiting friends, relatives, and locations from his boyhood towns of Shaw and Greenwood, Mississippi. Some images feature fellow blues musicians who appeared with Honeyboy in concerts and recording sessions. Original captions with Chatterley's contextual side comments were taken from back of prints. Arranged chronologically.
  - David "Honeyboy" Edwards just outside the back door at Rosa's Lounge on the 4th of July weekend, 1990, Chicago, Illinois (This was my first photo session with Honeyboy) (Box 15)
  - David "Honeyboy" Edwards with newly made friend, Chicago Blues Festival, 1991 June (contact negative) (Box 15)
  - Dvaid "Honeyboy" Edwards in the recording studio on New Year's Eve, 1991. Recording "Delta Bluesman" for Earwig Records. Chicago, Illinois (Box 15)
  - Sunnyland Slim (Albert Luandrew) in the recording studio for Honeyboy's "Delta Bluesman.' New Year's Eve, 1991 (Box 15)
  - Sunnyland Slim (Albert Luandrew) in the recording studio helping Honeyboy record "Delta Bluesman." Chicago, Illinois, New Year's Eve, 1991 (Box 15)
  - Carey Bell blowing harp for Honeyboy's "Delta Bluesman" recording in Chicago, Illinois, New Year's Eve, 1991 (Box 15)
  - David "Honeyboy" Edwards outside recording studio, Belmont Street, Chicago, Illinois (after recording for "Delta Bluesman." New Year's Eve, 1991 (Box 15)
  - David "Honeyboy" Edwards performing at the first Robert Johnson Memorial Blues Festival in Greenwood, Mississippi, June 1992. Perhaps the most spirited performance I ever saw him give. (Box 15)
  - David "Honeyboy" Edwards and John Hammond, Jr. at the 1st Annual Robert Johnson Blues Festival, Greenwood, Mississippi, 1992 June (two negatives printed consecutively) (Box 15)
  - Hallway bathroom in the Riverside Hotel, Clarksdale, Mississippi, 1992 June (Box 15)
  - David "Honeyboy" Edwards in the Riverside Hotel, Clarksdale, Mississippi, 1992 June (Box 15)
  - David "Honeyboy" Edwards showing dice tricks he learned from Big Joe Williams. The Riverside Hotel, Clarksdale, Mississippi, 1992 June (Box 15)
  - The David Lyndsay Band performing on a June Sunday morning near Maxwell Street, Chicago, Illinois, 1992. (Box 15)
  - Lonnie Pitchford and David "Honeyboy" Edwards backstage at the Chicago Blues Festival, 1992 June (Box 15)
  - Rosedale, Mississippi, 1992 June (Box 15)
  - Passing Parchman's Farm - Mississippi State Penitentiary, south of Tutwiler, 1992 July (Box 15)
  - David "Honeyboy" Edwards inside a small grocery store in Shaw, Mississippi-his hometown, 1992 July (Box 15)
  - David "Honeyboy" Edwards talking with some local folks on Johnson Street, Greenwood, Mississippi, 1992 July (Box 15)
  - David "Honeyboy" Edwards, live at Blind Willie's in Atlanta, Georgia, 1992 August (contact negatives) (Box 15)
  - Issaquena Street, downtown Clarksdale, Mississippi, 1992, Summer (Box 15)
  - Small grocer on Issaquena St., downtown Clarksdale, Mississippi, 1992 Summer (Box 15)
  - David "Honeyboy" Edwards purchasing a new wallet in a drug store in downtown Clarksdale, Mississippi. Two blocks away in the Delta Blues Museum at the Muddy Waters display, 1992 Summer (two 35mm negatives printed consecutively) (Box 15)
  - Left: Honeyboy visiting an old friend behind his cousin's repair shop, Shaw, Mississippi. Right: Honeyboy searching for his mother's unmarked gravesite, just outside Shaw, 1992 Summer (contact negatives) (Box 15)
  - David "Honeyboy" Edwards and another man sharing stories of people they both knew many years prior. Chris' Cafe, Greenwood, Mississippi, 1992 Summer (Box 15)
  - Men folding the state flag, Leflore County Courthouse, Greenwood, Mississippi, 1992 Summer (Box 15)
  - Storage building for Shellmound Plantation, outside Greenwood, Mississippi. This was once a county store and Honeyboy met Sonny Boy Williamson (Rice Miller) at this location. Honeyboy was 14 years old at the time, 1992 Summer (Box 15)
  - Bridge over the Tallahatchie River, outside Greenwood, Mississippi. Honeyboy walked this bridge countless times as a youth, 1992 Summer (Box 15)
  - David "Honeyboy" Edwards signing a copy of White Windows for Sonny Payne, Director of the radio station's King Biscuit Blues Hour in Helena, Arkansas. (Michael Frank, left), 1992 Summer (Box 15)
  - West Helena, Arkansas. For Honeyboy's "West Helena Blues" - the song with which he begins nearly every live performance, 1992 Summer (Box 16)
  - Eddie's Tavern, Helena, Arkansas, 1992 Summer (Box 16)
  - Helena, Arkansas, 1992 Summer (Box 16)
  - S. Rampart Street, New Orleans, Louisiana. Honeyboy said he lived on this block for a short time, 1992 Summer (Box 16)
  - New Orleans, Louisiana - from the I90 Bridge (Gentilly Blvd) looking toward the Interstate 10 Bridge, 1992 September (Box 16)
  - The location where Honeyboy Edwards met Robert Johnson (the lot just behind this young man) on Johnson Street, Greenwood, Mississippi, 1992 September (Box 16)
  - Seven contacts of the acreage where David "Honeyboy" Edwards birthplace home once stood 1 mile outside Shaw. The final two contacts are downtown Shaw, Mississippi, 1992 September (Box 16)
  - Abandoned house in Lula, north of Clarksdale, Mississippi, where Honeyboy lived for a short period of time in the 1940s, 1992 October (contact negative) (Box 16)
  - Abandoned bar near the Mississippi/Alabama border (east of Philadelphia, MS), 1992 Fall (Box 16)
  - Men burning the plastic off copper wire to salvage the contents for cash. Chicago's south side, 1992 (Box 16)
  - Wildwood Plantation near Money, Mississippi, where Honeyboy lived as a child. - The building, which was once a store, on Shellmound Plantation near Greenwood, Mississippi, where Honeyboy met Sonny Boy Williamson (Rice Miller). - The boyhood Missionary Baptist Church (Sweet Home M.B.C.) near Money, Mississippi. 1992, 3 contact prints (Box 16)
  - Man standing in downtown Tutwiler, Mississippi, across from where the train depot had been, and where W.C. Handy had his famous encounter with an old man playing the blues (when Handy woke from a nap) - Abandoned church near the burial place of Sonny Boy Williamson (Rice Miller) - Downtown Tutwiler again (same street, looking toward the train depot spot), 1992, 3 contact prints (Box 16)
  - From the Martin Luther King Bridge (crosses the Mississippi River), East St. Louis, Illinois. One of my two favorite landscape images in the entire body of work, 1993 March (Box 16)
  - Kentucky side of the Ohio/Mississippi River confluence - just south of Cairo, Illinois. High water, 1993 March (Box 16)
  - Honeyboy preparing for evening concert (we were snowed in). Scottish Inn, Chattanooga, Tennessee, 1993 March (Box 16)
  - Tuning up prior to performance. Chattanooga, Tennessee, 1993 March (Box 16)
  - Fish store, Clarksdale, Mississippi, 1993 March (Box 16)
  - Vicksburg, Mississippi, 1993 March (Box 16)
  - Civil War monument, Vicksburg, Mississippi, 1993 March (Box 16)
  - Bridge connecting Mississippi and Louisiana. Vicksburg, Miss, 1993 March (Box 16)
  - Downtown Shaw, Mississippi, hometown of David Honeyboy Edwards, 1993 March (Box 16)
  - Bridge over Tallahatchie River, near Ft. Loring (south of Greenwood), Mississippi, 1993 March (Box 16)
  - Beginning of a snow/sleet storm in Greenwood, Mississippi, 1993 March (Box 16)
  - Cemetery where Charlie Patton is buried, just outside Holly Ridge, Mississippi. Snow/sleet in March, 1993. (Box 16)
  - Elijah Newsome inside his World of Music (Blues shack). Itta Bena, Mississippi, 1993 March (Box 16)
  - Elijah Newsome's Blues shack, Itta Bena, Mississippi, 1993 March (Contact sheet print) (Box 16)
  - Bay St. Louis, Mississippi - near the location where Honeyboy and Big Joe Williams parted ways in the 1930s. One of my two favorite landscape images in the entire body of work, 1993 March (Box 16)
  - Fire, Erath, Louisiana, 1993 March (Box 17)
  - New Orleans, Louisiana, 1993 March (Street scene of telephone pole with "Thou Shalt Not Kill" sign.) (Box 17)